(Leonard:)Not heavy ones.
It's startling you haven't considered
a Lorentz invariant or field theory approach.
(Sheldon:)You think I haven't considered it?
(Sheldon:)- You really think I haven't considered it?
- Have you considered it?
- Get him out, Leonard.
- Come on, Dennis.
(Leonard:)I'll show you the radiation lab.
Wow. You won the Stevenson Award?
(Sheldon:)Yes. In fact,
I am the youngest person ever to win it.
Really? How old?
(Sheldon:)Fourteen and a half.
Mm. You were the youngest
ever to win it.
(Leonard:)It's like looking
into an obnoxious mirror, isn't it?
(Penny(to Raj):)Mm. This is really delicious, isn't it?
(Penny(to Raj):)Still can't talk to me
unless you're drunk, huh?
(Penny(to Raj):)Oh, sweetie, you are so damaged.
(Howard:)Hey, I'm damaged too.